Guide to the Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center Photographs 1919-1969
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 1: Images created by WSU-Prosser staff, 1919-1969
  - Subseries 1: Dated images, 1919-1969
    - Fall, 1941. Lima Bean Fertilizer Plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941 (Box 4, Item 41.011)
    - Fall, 1941. Lima Bean Field. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941 (Box 4, Item 41.012)
    - Fall, 1941. Lima Bean Fertilizer Plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941 (Box 4, Item 41.013)
    - Fall, 1941. Lima Bean Fertilizer Plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941 (Box 4, Item 41.014)
    - Fall, 1941. Lima Bean Fertilizer Plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941 (Box 4, Item 41.015)
    - Fall, 1941. Sweet potato varieties. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941 (Box 4, Item 41.016)
    - Plot 10A. Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.018)
    - Plot 18. Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.019)
    - Plot 9A. Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.020)
    - Plot 6. Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.021)
    - Plot 9. Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.022)
    - Plot 23A. Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.023)
    - Plot 20A. Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.024)
    - Walla Walla fertilizer plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.025)
    - Walla Walla fertilizer plots - Plot 16A. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.026)
    - Walla Walla - Plot 9. 5x7 neg.; 4 prints. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.027)
    - Walla Walla- Lower tier of fertilizer plots. Two cars. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.028)
    - Walla Walla- Lower tier of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-10-24 (Box 4, Item 41.029)
    - Plot 10 - North fertilizer plots - Corn. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.030)
    - Plot 9 - North fertilizer plots - Corn. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.031)
    - Plot 6 - North fertilizer plots - Corn. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.032)
    - Plot 5 - North fertilizer plots - Corn. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.033)
    - Plot 4 - North fertilizer plots - Corn. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.034)
    - Plot 3 - North fertilizer plots - Corn. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.035)
    - Plot 1 - North fertilizer plots - Corn. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.036)
    - Plot 2 - North fertilizer plots - Corn. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.037)
    - Plot 11- North fertilizer plots. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.038)
    - Plot 12- North fertilizer plots. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.039)
    - Plot 14- North fertilizer plots. N of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-11-25 (Box 4, Item 41.040)
    - Medina apples. 5x7 neg. 1941-10-01 (Box 4, Item 41.041)
    - Medina apples. 5x7 neg. 1941-10-01 (Box 4, Item 41.042)
    - Strawberry fertilizers. Front right - treated (Starter sol.). Back right - untreated. D1. 5x7 neg. 1941-06-02 (Box 4, Item 41.043)
    - Strawberry fertilizers. Front right - treated (Starter sol.). Back right - untreated. D1. 5x7 neg. 1941-06-02 (Box 4, Item 41.044)
    - Tree - 14 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1941-12-26 (Box 4, Item 41.045)
    - Tree - 8 K. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1941-12-26 (Box 4, Item 41.046)
    - Starch- storage samples. Basement. 5x7 neg. 1941-01-02 (Box 4, Item 41.047)
    - Starch- storage samples. Basement. 5x7 neg. 1941-01-02 (Box 4, Item 41.048)
    - Starch- storage samples. Basement. 5x7 neg. 1941-01-02 (Box 4, Item 41.049)
    - Storage - apple plots -2 I, J, K, L; 4 I, J, K, L; 6 I, J, K, L and 8J. Basement. 5x7 neg. 1941-02-14 (Box 4, Item 41.050)
    - Starch - storage samples. 8 K, L; 10 I, J, K, L, C; 12 L; 5 K, L; 14 8, I, J. Basement. 5x7 neg. 1941-01-02 (Box 4, Item 41.051)
    - Starch - storage samples. 16 I, J, K, L; 18 I, J, K, L; 20 I, J, K, L. Basement. 5x7 neg. 1941-01-02 (Box 4, Item 41.052)
    - Winesap storage apples. 8 K, L; 10 I, J, K, L, 10C; 12 I, J, K, L; 14 I, J. Basement. 5x7 neg. 1941-02-14 (Box 4, Item 41.053)
    - Winesap storage apples. 16 I,J, K, L; 18 I,J, K, L; 20 I, J, K, L. Basement. 5x7 neg. 1941-02-14 (Box 4, Item 41.054)
    - Tree 16 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-04 (Box 4, Item 42.001)
    - Tree 20 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.002)
    - Tree 18 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.003)
    - Tree 16 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.005)
    - Tree 14 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.006)
    - Tree 14 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.007)
    - Tree 12 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.009)
    - Tree 10 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.010)
    - Tree 10 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.011)
    - Tree 8 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.012)
    - Tree 8 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.013)
    - Hay stacks. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-21 (Box 4, Item 42.014)
    - Feed lots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-21 (Box 4, Item 42.015)
    - Snow Scene. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-21 (Box 4, Item 42.017)
    - Snow Scene - around grounds. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-21 (Box 4, Item 42.018)
    - Tree 20 G. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.019)
    - Tree18 G. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.020)
    - Tree16 G. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.021)
    - Tree14 G. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.022)
    - Tree12 G. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.023)
    - Tree10 G. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.024)
    - Tree 8 G. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.025)
    - Tree 6 G. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.026)
    - Tree Del. 6 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.027)
    - Tree Del. 4 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.028)
    - Tree Del. 2 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.029)
    - Tree 4 E. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.030)
    - Tree G 2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.031)
    - Tree 2 K. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.032)
    - Tree 4 K. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.033)
    - Tree 6 K. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-02-06 (Box 4, Item 42.034)
    - Tree20 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.035)
    - Feeders' Day. 3.25x4.25 neg.; print. 1942-04-21 (Box 4, Item 42.036)
    - Feeders' Day. 3.25x4.25 neg.; print. 1942-04-21 (Box 4, Item 42.037)
    - Feeders' Day. 3.25x4.25 neg.; print. 1942-04-21 (Box 4, Item 42.038)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.25x4.25 neg.; print. 1942-04-22 (Box 4, Item 42.039)
    - Tree 18 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.040)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1942-04-22 (Box 4, Item 42.040)
    - Beef cattle. Feed lots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-04 (Box 4, Item 42.041)
    - Beef cattle. Feed lots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-04 (Box 4, Item 42.042)
    - Beef cattle. Feed lots. 5x7 neg. 1942-04 (Box 4, Item 42.043)
    - Beef cattle. Feed lots. 5x7 neg. 1942-04 (Box 4, Item 42.044)
    - Forty Fold wheat in alfalfa. South of Plots C2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-06-22 (Box 4, Item 42.045)
    - Alfalfa Cultivation Experiment - Fall and spring cultivated alfalfa. West of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-06-22 (Box 4, Item 42.046)
    - Alfalfa Cultivation Experiment - Forty Fold wheat in alfalfa. East of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-06-22 (Box 4, Item 42.047)
    - Alfalfa Cultivation Experiment - Check plot. Cheat in alfalfa. West of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-06-22 (Box 4, Item 42.048)
    - Alfalfa Cultivation Experiment - Check plot. Cheat in alfalfa. West of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-06-22 (Box 4, Item 42.049)
    - Forty Fold wheat in alfalfa. East of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-06-22 (Box 4, Item 42.050)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 13. N - 80, P - 80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.051)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 8 A. N - 160, P - 80, K -80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.052)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 1 A. N - 80, P - 80, K - 80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.053)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 2 A. Check. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.054)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 2 A. Check. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.055)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 14. N -80, P - 80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.056)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 19 - Straw. N - 160, P - 80. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.057)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot24(22?) - Straw. N - 160, K - 80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.058)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 21 - Straw. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.059)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 20 - Straw. N - 160. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.060)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 19 - Straw. P, K. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.061)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 17 - Rye. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.062)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 18 - Rye + N. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.063)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 24(19?) - Straw. P - 80, K - 80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.064)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 22 - Straw. N - 160. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.065)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 20 - Straw. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.066)
    - Walla Walla Plots-Plot 22(24?). Straw. N-160, P-80, K-80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.067)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 22. Straw. N-160, K-80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.068)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 23. Straw. N-160, P-80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.069)
    - Walla Walla Plots-Plot 23(24?). Straw. N-160, P-80, K-80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.070)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 3 A. Manure - 16 tons. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.071)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 16. Alfalfa hay - 3.2 tons. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.072)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 7 A. N - 80. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.073)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 5 A. Manure - 8 tons, P - 40. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.074)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 4 A. Manure - 8 tons. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.075)
    - Walla Walla Plots - Plot 15. Alfalfa hay 1.6 tons. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-08 (Box 4, Item 42.076)
    - Emerald - Plot 6, Barley. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.077)
    - Emerald - Plot 5, Poor barley on non-flooded land. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.078)
    - Emerald - Plot 5, Healthy barley on flooded land. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.079)
    - Tree 2 C. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-01-12 (Box 4, Item 42.080)
    - Emerald - Plot 5, Barley. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.080)
    - Emerald - Plot 7, Barley. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.081)
    - Emerald - Plot 8, Barley. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.082)
    - Emerald - Plot 9, Barley. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.083)
    - Emerald - Plot 2, Barley. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.084)
    - Emerald - Plot 1, Barley. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.085)
    - Emerald - Plot 1, Barley. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.086)
    - Emerald - Plot 4, Barley. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.087)
    - Emerald - Plot 3, Barley. 5x7 neg. 1942-07-23 (Box 4, Item 42.088)
    - D 1, Second Plant - Cage Experiment. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-28 (Box 4, Item 42.089)
    - D 1, Second Plant - Cage Experiment. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-28 (Box 4, Item 42.090)
    - D 1, Squash Bug Cage Experiment. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-28 (Box 4, Item 42.091)
    - D 1, Squash Bug Cage Experiment. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-28 (Box 4, Item 42.092)
    - Little Rubber (?) Plants, Cold Creek Road. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-31 (Box 4, Item 42.093)
    - Little Rubber (?) Plants, Cold Creek Road. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-07-31 (Box 4, Item 42.094)
    - Plot 9 - Alfalfa hay. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.095)
    - Plot 8 - Check. Alfalfa hay. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.096)
    - Plot 6 - Horse Manure. Alfalfa hay. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.097)
    - Plot 5 - Fish Scraps. Alfalfa hay. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.098)
    - Plot 4 - Alfalfa hay. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.099)
    - Plot 11 - Alfalfa hay. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.100)
    - Plot 2 - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. Sodium nitrate. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.101)
    - Plot 2 - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. Sodium nitrate. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.102)
    - Plot 1 - Alfalfa hay. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.103)
    - Plot 12 - Alfalfa hay. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.104)
    - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots - Plot 20 - (NH4) SO + Straw. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.105)
    - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots - Plot 19 - NPK. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.106)
    - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots - Plot 18 - Check. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.107)
    - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots - Plot 17 - PK. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.108)
    - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots - Plot 17 - PK. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.109)
    - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots - Plot 15 - NP. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.110)
    - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots - Plot 14 - Complete + Straw. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.111)
    - Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots - Plot 10 - Sheep Manure. N. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-08-01 (Box 4, Item 42.112)
    - Clore and Singleton in field of edible soybeans. Singleton and Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP159. 1942-08-12 (Box 4, Item 42.113)
    - Clore and Menzies in field of edible soybeans. Field D4. Clore and Menzies. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP160. 1942-08-12 (Box 4, Item 42.115)
    - Lathyrus sylvestris- 1) Phyllosy, 2) Healthy, 3) Dwarf. Shade of Office. 5x7 neg. 1942-08-29 (Box 4, Item 42.116)
    - Cattle chute and ring latches. 5x7 neg. 1942-08-29 (Box 4, Item 42.117)
    - Cattle chute - inside view. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP161. 1942-08-29 (Box 4, Item 42.118)
    - Cattle chute - side view. 5x7 neg. 1942-08-29 (Box 4, Item 42.119)
    - Cattle chute - side view. Station. 5x7 neg. 1942-08-29 (Box 4, Item 42.120)
    - Phyllopdy on Lathyrus sylvestris. 5x7 neg. 1942-08-17 (Box 4, Item 42.121)
    - Corn - Rotation 2, Plot 216. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.122)
    - Corn - Rotation 52, Plot 603. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.123)
    - Corn - Rotation 76, Plot 406. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.124)
    - Corn - Rotation 25A, Plot 504. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.125)
    - Spuds - Rotation 22B (C?), Plot 8. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.126)
    - Spuds - Rotation 22B, Plot 4. 5x7 neg. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.127)
    - Spuds - Rotation 76, Plot 405. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.128)
    - Potatoes - Rotation 78A, Plot 612. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.129)
    - Spuds - Rotation 50, Plot 507. 5x7 neg.; 2 prints. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.130)
    - Spuds - Rotation 78-A, Plot 612. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.131)
    - Spuds - Rotation 52, Plot 604. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.132)
    - Spuds - Rotation 72, Plot 211. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.133)
    - Beets - Rotation 78, Plot 516. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.134)
    - Beets - Rotation 78A, Plot 611. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.135)
    - Beets - Rotation 8, Plot 217. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.136)
    - Beets - Rotation, Plot 116. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.137)
    - Beets - Rotation 70, Plot 106. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.138)
    - Beets - Rotation 40, Plot 108. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.139)
    - Beets - Rotation 72, Plot 209. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.140)
    - Alfalfa Border effect - Rotation 72, Plot 207. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.141)
    - Rotation 26, Plot 27. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.142)
    - Rotation 40A, Plot 215. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.143)
    - Headlands - Brome Grass - Plot 604 in Rotations. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.144)
    - Rotation 40 A, Plot 212. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-21 (Box 4, Item 42.145)
    - Rotation 23, Plot 503. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-22 (Box 4, Item 42.146)
    - 2% Contour. North of 2% contour. 5x7 neg. 1942-09-14 (Box 4, Item 42.147)
    - 2% Contour plots. North of 2% contour. S.C.S. 5x7 neg. 1942-09-14 (Box 4, Item 42.148)
    - 3% Contour. West of plots. S.C.S. 5x7 neg. 1942-09-14 (Box 4, Item 42.149)
    - Contour plots. S.C.S. West of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-14 (Box 4, Item 42.150)
    - 3% Contour plots. North of 3% Contour. S.C.S. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-11 (Box 4, Item 42.151)
    - Down Slope plots. S.C.S. South side of Down Slope. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-11 (Box 4, Item 42.152)
    - Down Slope plots. S.C.S. West of plot. 5x7 neg. 1942-09-11 (Box 4, Item 42.153)
    - Plot 2A, Grimm. S.of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.154)
    - Plot 3A, Ladok. S.of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.155)
    - Plot 4A, Utah Pioneer. S.of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.156)
    - Plot 11A. S.of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.157)
    - Plot 12A, Check. S.of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.158)
    - Plot 6B, Washington Common. S.of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.159)
    - Plot 8B, Hardistan. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.160)
    - Plot 7B, Cosack. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.161)
    - Plot 9B, Arizona Common. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.162)
    - Plot 10B, Utah Common. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.163)
    - Plot 16. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.164)
    - Plot 19, Kansas Common. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.165)
    - Plot 16B. 5x7 neg.; print. 1942-09-19 (Box 4, Item 42.166)
    - Potato Virus- L to R. 1.Naturally infected, 2.Healthy, 3.by grafting (1 month). N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1942-10-19 (Box 4, Item 42.167)
    - Potato Witches Broom. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1942-10-19 (Box 4, Item 42.168)
    - Tree 20 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.169)
    - Tree 20 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.170)
    - Tree 18 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.171)
    - Tree 18 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.172)
    - Tree 16 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.173)
    - Tree 16 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.174)
    - Tree 12 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.175)
    - Tree 12 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.176)
    - Tree 10 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.177)
    - Tree 10 I. Tree to S.E. 5x7 neg. 1942-01-02 (Box 4, Item 42.178)
    - Feeders' Day Crowd. Location - Prosser. 3.25x4.25 neg. WSUP162. 1943-03-23 (Box 4, Item 43.001)
    - Feeders' Day Crowd. Super Pan Press. Location -. 3.25x4.25 neg. WSUP163. 1943-03-23 (Box 4, Item 43.002)
    - First irrigation-border method. Emerald. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-04-26 (Box 4, Item 43.004)
    - Asparagus injury by wind. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1943-05-08 (Box 4, Item 43.005)
    - L to R -Alta Fescus, Meadow Fescue, Orchard grass. 5x7 neg. 1943-06-10 (Box 4, Item 43.006)
    - L to R -Chewing Fescus, Creeping Red Fescue, Sheep Fescue. 5x7 neg. 1943-06-10 (Box 4, Item 43.007)
    - L to R -Creeping Red Fescue, Sheep Fescue, Red Fescue. Grass Nursery. 5x7 neg. 1943-06-10 (Box 4, Item 43.008)
    - L to R -Beardless Wheat Grass, Slender Wheat Grass, Smooth Brome Grass. 5x7 neg. 1943-06-11 (Box 4, Item 43.009)
    - L to R -Canada Rye Grass, Canada Rye Grass, Orchard Grass. Grass Nursery. 5x7 neg. 1943-06-11 (Box 4, Item 43.010)
    - L to R - Non-shattering Tall Oat, Red Top, Tall oat grass. Grass Nursery. 5x7 neg. 1943-06-11 (Box 4, Item 43.011)
    - Poa Ampla (Big Bluegrass). 5x7 neg. 1943-06-11 (Box 4, Item 43.012)
    - R to L - Reed Canary Grass, Volunteer Sweet Clover. North of plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-06-11 (Box 4, Item 43.013)
    - L to R - Timothy, Mountain Rye, Bulbous Barley. 5x7 neg. 1943-06-11 (Box 4, Item 43.014)
    - Varieties of alfalfa in foreground.Tall Fescue in background. 5x7 neg. 1943-06-11 (Box 4, Item 43.015)
    - Plot 501, Crop Rotation Plots. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-07-28 (Box 4, Item 43.016)
    - Plot 503, Crop Rotation Plots. N. of plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-07-28 (Box 4, Item 43.017)
    - Plot 211, Crop Rotation Plots. N. of plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-07-28 (Box 4, Item 43.018)
    - Plot 212, Crop Rotation Plots. N. of plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-07-28 (Box 4, Item 43.019)
    - Plot 601, Crop Rotation Plots. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-07-28 (Box 4, Item 43.020)
    - Potatoes - Plot 210. Rotation 72. No neg. 1943-10-10 (Box 4, Item 43.021)
    - Corn - Plot 214. Rotation 44A. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.022)
    - Corn - Plot 514. Rotation 78. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.023)
    - Corn - Plot 612. Rotation 78A. 3.25x4.25 neg.; 3 prints. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.024)
    - Potatoes - Plot 110. Rotation 40. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.025)
    - Potatoes - Plot 313. Rotation 74. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.026)
    - Potatoes - Plot 404. Rotation 76. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.027)
    - Potatoes - Plot 506. Rotation 50. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.028)
    - Potatoes - Plot 611. Rotation 78A. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.029)
    - Potatoes - Plot 615. Rotation 22A. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.030)
    - Sugar Beets - Plot 214. Rotation 40A. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.031)
    - Sugar Beets - Plot 314. Rotation 74. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.032)
    - Sugar Beets - Plot 515. Rotation 78. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.033)
    - Sugar Beets - Plot 610. Rotation 78A. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1943-10-14 (Box 4, Item 43.034)
    - Detasseling corn on horseback. 3.25x4.25 neg. WSUP164. 1943 (Box 4, Item 43.035)
    - Detasseling corn on horseback. L - Esther Jones, R - Alice Monden. E. Jones, A.Monden. 3.25x4.25 neg. WSUP165. 1943 (Box 4, Item 43.036)
    - Feeders' Day Crowd. Feed lots. 3.25x4.25 neg. WSUP166. 1943-03-23 (Box 4, Item 43.038)
    - Turkestan - Plot 11. E. of plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-09-21 (Box 4, Item 43.039)
    - Turkestan - Plot 11. W. of plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-09-21 (Box 4, Item 43.040)
    - Turkestan Alfalfa Plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-09-21 (Box 4, Item 43.041)
    - Turkestan Alfalfa Plot. W. of plot. 5x7 neg. 1943-09-21 (Box 4, Item 43.042)
    - Pear Disease. 5x7 neg. 1943 (Box 4, Item 43.043)
    - Pear Specimens: 1.Station corkspot, 2.Corkspot (?) Lindner, 3. Corkspot + ringing - Lindner, 4. Smalling or - necrotic type, 5. Boron def. Kienholz, 6. Stony pit - Kienholz. 5x7 neg. 1943 (Box 4, Item 43.044)
    - No identification. 1944 (Box 4, Item 44.000)
    - No identification. 1944 (Box 4, Item 44.001)
    - Fertilizer Drill. Earl Plank. 5x7 neg. WSUP167. 1944-04-05 (Box 4, Item 44.002)
    - Fertilizer Drill. Carrot field. 5x7 neg. 1944-04-22 (Box 4, Item 44.003)